webpackJsonp([1],{Fvg5:function(e,s,t){"use strict";var a=function(){var e=this,s=e.$createElement,t=e._self._c||s;return t("div",{staticClass:"screen",attrs:{id:"app"}},[t("div",{staticClass:"screen-outer"},[t("div",{staticClass:"screen-glare"}),t("div",{staticClass:"screen-inner"},[0==e.phase?t("div",{staticClass:"start"},[t("h1",{staticClass:"start-title"},[e._v("programming language test")]),e.loading?e._e():t("p",{staticClass:"start-notification"},[e._v("press enter to start test")]),t("span",{staticClass:"team"},[e._v("pxlhead tm")]),e.loading?t("div",{staticClass:"loader"},[t("span",{staticClass:"loader-title"},[e._v("Loading")]),t("span",{staticClass:"loader-bar"},[e._v(e._s(e.loaderBar))])]):e._e()]):e._e(),1==e.phase?t("div",{staticClass:"test"},[t("h3",{staticClass:"test-question"},[e._v(e._s(e.activeTest.question))]),t("div",{staticClass:"test-answers"},e._l(e.activeTest.answers,function(s,a){return t("span",{staticClass:"answer",class:{"answer--active":a==e.activeAnswer},on:{click:function(s){e.activeAnswer=a}}},[e._v(e._s(s))])}))]):e._e(),2==e.phase?t("div",{staticClass:"result"},[e.loading?t("div",{staticClass:"loader"},[t("span",{staticClass:"loader-title"},[e._v(e._s(e.loaderText))])]):t("div",{staticClass:"result-message"},[t("h3",{staticClass:"result-text"},[e._v("Try not. Do "+e._s(e.result)+" ‚Äì or do not "+e._s(e.result)+". There is no try.")]),t("span",{staticClass:"result-notification"},[e._v("Enter press to restart and be mindful.")])])]):e._e()])])])},i=[],n={render:a,staticRenderFns:i};s.a=n},Kbsk:function(e,s,t){"use strict";s.a={question:"What is your purpose of studying?",answers:["Web development","Software development","Mobile app development"],0:{question:"Do you like interacting with people?",answers:["I'm good with people","I hate them all"],0:{question:"Are you a creative person?",answers:["I'm a man of beauty","Functionality is more important for me"],0:"HTML + CSS",1:"JS"},1:{question:"Are you a workaholic?",answers:["Personal life is more important for me","Work is my credo"],0:{question:"Are you conservative or liberal?",answers:["I love sorting out retro things","I'm futurist"],0:"PHP",1:"Node.js"},1:{question:"What kind kind of music do you prefer?",answers:["Retrowave","Power metal","Alternative","Pop"],0:"C#",1:"Java",2:"Ruby",3:"Python"}}},1:{question:"How do you usually spend your free time?",answers:["Gaming!","Reinstalling OS","Thinking of business ideas","Building my own C-3PO","Doing my homework"],0:{question:"Which type of game you play last time?",answers:["Indie","AAA","Text","MMORPG"],0:{question:"Which styles of visual art do you prefer?",answers:["Realism","Surrealism","Cubism","Post-modernism","Avant-garde","Primitivism"],0:"C++",1:"C#",2:"Java",3:"Python",4:"JS",5:"Delphi"},1:{question:"What is you favourite weapon in games?",answers:["Bow to shot at someone's knee üèπ","Magic/Biotics/Psyonics","Knife (no matter what game it is)"],0:"C++",1:"C#",2:"Java"},2:{question:"Which type of literature whould you choose?",answers:["Fantasy","Sci-fi","Manual/Docs/Guide","Documentary","Classic","Novel","Comics (OMG)"],0:"C++",1:"C#",2:"Java",3:"Python",4:"Delphi",5:"JS",6:"ActionScript"},3:{question:"Which fictional race would you like to be?",answers:["Hafling","Dwarf","Klingon","Borg","Wookiee","Azari","Troll"],0:"C++",1:"C#",2:"Java",3:"Python",4:"Delphi",5:"JS",6:"ActionScript"}},1:{question:"Which OS do you reinstall?",answers:["Windows üò©","Linux (reboot now)","MacOS"],0:{question:"Which character would you be in the world of LOTR?",answers:["J. R. R. Tolkien","Sauron","Gandalf","What is LOTR?","Treebeard","Dumbledore"],0:"C",1:"C++",2:"Java",3:"Rust",4:"Delphi",5:"Visual Basic"},1:{question:"Which fiction film do you like?",answers:["Star Trek (old)","Star Trek (new)","Star Wars","Men in black","Space Odyssey","Interstellar"],0:"C",1:"C++",2:"Java",3:"Python",4:"Delphi",5:"Go"},2:{question:"Where would you spend your holidays?",answers:["Home","Parent's home","Friend's home","Silicon Valley","Holidays?"],0:"C",1:"C++",2:"Objective-C",3:"Swift",4:"Java"}},2:{question:"Which way would you choose to conquer the world?",answers:["Political","Economical","Social","Military"],0:"C++",1:"Java",2:"Python",3:"Ada"},3:{question:"Which genre of fiction do you prefer?",answers:["Steampunk","Sci-fi","Cyberpunk"],0:"Assembler",1:"C",2:"Go"},4:{question:"Which subject would be the first?",answers:["Math","Economics","Statistics","Informatics","Physics"],0:"Matlab",1:"Java",2:"R",3:"Python",4:"C"}},2:{question:"CEO of which company would you like to be?",answers:["Apple","Google","Windows"],0:{question:"Which coffee do you like?",answers:["Latte","–°appuccino","Espresso"],0:"Swift",1:"Objective-C",2:"Java"},1:{question:"Which cuisine do you like?",answers:["Chinese","European","Elvish","Mexican"],0:"Objective-C",1:"Java",2:"JS",3:"Python"},2:{question:"Which cuisine do you like?",answers:["Chinese","European","Elvish","Mexican"],0:"Objective-C",1:"Java",2:"JS",3:"Python"}}}},M93x:function(e,s,t){"use strict";function a(e){t("PQM+")}var i=t("xJD8"),n=t("Fvg5"),o=t("VU/8"),r=a,l=o(i.a,n.a,r,null,null);s.a=l.exports},NHnr:function(e,s,t){"use strict";Object.defineProperty(s,"__esModule",{value:!0});var a=t("7+uW"),i=t("M93x");a.a.config.productionTip=!1,new a.a({el:"#app",template:"<App/>",components:{App:i.a}})},"PQM+":function(e,s){},xJD8:function(e,s,t){"use strict";var a=t("Kbsk");s.a={name:"app",data:function(){return{phase:0,loading:!1,loaderBar:"",loaderPhrases:["Collecting your answers...","Comparing answers with PL matrix...","Testing your patience...","Analizing..."],activePhrase:0,activeAnswer:0,answersStack:[],result:""}},mounted:function(){document.addEventListener("keydown",this.onKeydown)},computed:{activeTest:function(){var e=a.a;return this.answersStack.forEach(function(s){e=e[s]}),"string"!=typeof e?e:(this.showResult(e),{})},loaderText:function(){if(-1!=this.activePhrase)return this.loaderPhrases[this.activePhrase]}},methods:{showResult:function(e){var s=this;this.phase=2,this.loading=!0,this.result=e;var t=setInterval(function(){return s.activePhrase++},1500);setTimeout(function(){clearInterval(t),s.loading=!1,s.activePhrase=0},1500*this.loaderPhrases.length)},onKeydown:function(e){var s=this;if(0==this.phase&&13==e.keyCode){this.loading=!0;var t=setInterval(function(){return s.loaderBar+="#"},500);setTimeout(function(){clearInterval(t),s.loading=!1,s.phase=1},3e3)}else 1==this.phase?13==e.keyCode?(this.answersStack.push(this.activeAnswer),this.activeAnswer=0):38==e.keyCode?this.activeAnswer=this.activeAnswer>0?this.activeAnswer-1:this.activeTest.answers.length-1:40==e.keyCode&&(this.activeAnswer=this.activeAnswer<this.activeTest.answers.length-1?this.activeAnswer+1:0):13==e.keyCode&&(this.phase=0,this.answersStack=[],this.loaderBar="")}}}}},["NHnr"]);
//# sourceMappingURL=app.dd43cd118c49c6b81658.js.map